and be
to [sing] a surprises you and meat
rank up [music]
coming rank up
your way to the
upus [sing]
and be
[sing]
a quality [music] that surprises you
and meat
rank [sing] up coming rank up
your way to the
ram
was [sing] empty
commed to a [music] quality that
surprises you and me the rank
[music][sing] up coming rank up
your way to [music][sing]
R
family to me [music]
teaching me the [sing] things that
I should be
be famous and [sing] be committed
to a quality that surprises you and meak
up coming rank up [music]
start your way to the Dong
hello
new days, new vlogs.
[whistles]
So last time you guys
went solo, now [sighs] it's
as a love team.
[music] Are
you ready?  Ready.  Yes.
Whoever has the best acting will be
given a prize and will receive
Php5,000.
Okay, let's start the acting
challenge right away.  We'll start with
Ms and Glay.
Y [cheers]
okay.  The sun is with us.
Okay, mix, choose numbers 1 to 10,
number two, okay, choose numbers
1 to 10.  Okay.  Number one,
Migs' line is, "This is me, Natoy, who
loves you very much."
The line is "but why does it feel
like it's my fault?"
Ready?  Ready.  Okay.  Midly ready?  You
start.  Happy.  But why is it
my fault?
Yes, that's right.  Natuy loves you very much.
But why does it feel like it's my fault?   This is
me [music],
Natoy.  That you are so loved.
Disappointed.
But why does it feel like it's my fault?  This is me,
Natoy.  That you are so loved.
Swirty.
But why does it feel like it's my fault?   It's
me.  Father?   I
love you so much [music]
angry
why is this like my wedding? I'm so in
love with you so much
angry
why is this like my wedding?
Who is it that loves you so much
[cheers]
let's immediately follow the angry
John Michael and Francesca.
[cheers]
[applause]
Okay.  Janeska ready?  Ready, boss.
Okay.  JM choose from 1 to 10 except
number two.
Six.
Number six.  You are Chess.  You are chosen 1 to
10 except number one seven times.  Okay JM,
your line is what I want.
Pasuplada effect playing hard to get.
Cheska, your line is, don't
do that again.  Okay, ready.  You say you're the
first and ready.  Happy.  Don't
do that again.
That's what I want.  Boost effect.
Playing hard to get.  Sad.
Don't do that again.  That's what
I want.  Boost effect.  Playing hard
to get.  Disappointed.
Don't do that again.
That's the [music] I like.  Boost
effect.   The
one who plays hard to get.  flirty.  Don't
do that again.
What I like
is the boost effect.
The
playing hard to get
angry.  Don't do that again.
[music]
That's what I want.
[clears throat]
The pasuplate effect.  The one who plays hard
to get.
Together.  Together.  Together.
That's what I want.
That kind of sloppy effect.  You're playing
hard to get.
[whispering]
Okay.  Will Janeska win later?
Next, let's plant the Kenla and the
hala.
Okay.  Kenneth, Ella
and Hay are with us.  In this situation, there are three of
you.  So you, Kenneth and Haid will choose
numbers from 1 to 10 except 2
and 6. And you, Ella, will
also choose numbers from 1 to 10 except 1 and
7. Okay.  What's your number?  Seven.
Kenneth, number three.  Number three.
Ella number
10.
10. Your line is okay Kenneth,
you are not Celine and you will never be
Celine.
And you, by the way, the number you chose is
seven.  Your line is something you think doesn't exist,
but it does.  There is something.   What do you
think, Ella, it's your fault if
you don't love me?  Oh,
ready?
Ready.
Okay.  Let's start with you, Ella.
Happy.   It's
not your fault if you don't
love me.  Yes, yes.   It's
love me.
You just thought there wasn't anything, but there is.
Yes.
[music]
Ra.
You're not Silin, are you?  And you will
never be Celine.   It's
not your fault if you don't
love me.   It's
love me.
You just thought it was nothing.  But there is.
Yes.  Yes.
No.  You are Shelin and you will never
be Selin.
Disappointed.   It's
not your fault if you don't
love me.   It's
love me.
You just thought it was nothing.  But there is, there is
.  You are not Celin
and you will never be Celin.  Flirty.   It's
not your fault if you don't
love me.  [music] It's
your fault if you don't
love me.
You just think there's nothing
but there is, there is,
you're not Celin and you will never
be [music] Celine.
Agreed.  It's not your fault if
you don't love me.   It's
not your fault if you don't
love me.  Very angry.  It's not your
fault if you don't love me.   It's
not your fault if you don't
love me.  [music] You're welcome.
But there is.  Yes.  Yes.  Very
angry.  [music] You just thought it was nothing.  But
there is, there is.
You are not Celine and you will never
be Celine.  Very angry.  You are not
Celine and you will never be Celine.
Okay.  The next one to be introduced is
John L.
[applause]
John Ashley and Luis are
us.  Okay.  John Lou, like the
previous ones, you can choose from numbers from 1
to 10 except 2 3 6 and 7.
Number eight.
Number eight.  Luis avoid numbers 1, 7
and 10. Number eight.  Wow.  Eight.
Lucky number.  John Ashley.
Just bet.  If we get hurt, etc.
That will hurt your line.  And to you, Luis.
Yes.  Yes.  I'm just your friend.
I'm just your friend.  Okay.  We'll start with you,
Luis.  Ready?
Ready.
Okay.  Cy.
Yes.  Yes.  I am your friend.
I'm just your friend.
Just bet if we get hurt.  Oh, it will
hurt.  Where?
Yes.
I am your friend.
I'm just your friend.
Just bet [music]
if we get hurt.
It can get hurt.  disappointed.
Yes.
I am your friend.
I'm just your friend.  Just bet.
If we get hurt [music]
Edda will hurt.
flirty?
Oh
yes.
I am your friend.
I'm just your [music] friend.
You'll be fine later
if [music]
hurts us.
Eli will be hurt.  Angry.  [music]
Yes.
I am your friend.
I'm just your friend [music].  You know,
just bet
if we get hurt.  ' Hurt.
Very angry.  Just bet.  If
we get hurt.  You know it won't hurt.
Very angry, Luis.  Yes.
Yes.  I am your friend.  I'm just your friend
.  [squeaking]
[cheers]
Next up is Rain and
the Gelsea.
[applause]
Okay.  Rain, Angel and Cassie.  Just like
Heila and Kenla earlier, the same
scenario will happen to you.  Rain, choose
a number except 2 3 6 7 8 10.
Number 10. Because you are number
one.  Okay.  Angel, choose a number.
Number nine.  Number nine.
Your line, Rain, is that none of you are
asking if I'm okay.
And you, your line is "my god" which is a
long noun.  Okay, angel number
nine, you don't know how I feel.
Okay, let's start.  Happy,
you don't know how I feel.
You have no idea how I feel.
My god, it's a long-lasting noun.  None
of you are asking questions.  I'm okay.  Okay,
you have no idea how I feel.
You have no idea how
I feel.
My goodness [music] has been around for a
long time.   There's
nothing wrong with you.  asking
if I'm okay.  Disappointed.
You have no idea how I feel.
My god K. It's been a
long time.  None
of you are.
Asking if I'm okay.  [music]
30.
You don't know how I feel.
You have no idea how I feel.   Oh
my god.  Just a little while.  None
of you.  [Music] asks if
I'm okay.
You don't know how I feel.
Very angry.
You have no idea how I feel.
You have no idea how I feel.  Very
angry.  You know you don't know anything about
[crying] how I feel.  Angry.
My god, it's been a long time.  Very
angry.  My god, it's been a long time.
Very angry.  My god, it's been a
long time.  None
of you are.  Asking questions?
I'm okay.  Very angry.  No one is
asking you questions.
If I were okay, I would be angrier.  No one is
asking you to leave
if I'm okay.
[applause]
[cheers] Okay.  Let's see if
Rain Angel and Cassie can win
this round.  [applause]
[cheers]
Next in the living room is the big
[applause]
with us, Yana and Brion.
Brion, the remaining numbers are 4, 5 and
9. What number would you choose?  Number
five.  Number five.  That's it, the
remaining numbers are 2 3 4 5 and 6. Six.
Six.  Okay.
Your line [clears throat].  Brion,
you only love me when we are happy.  W
[singing]
and to you Yana, you won't be sorry.   Say
sorry.  Say sorry.
Please apologize.
That's it.  You go first.  Ready?  Ready.
Okay.  Happy.  You won't be sorry.   Say
sorry.  Say sorry.   Say
sorry.  Please.
You only love me when we are happy.
Where?
You're sorry.   Say
sorry.  Say sorry.   Say
sorry.  Please
only love me [music] when
we are happy.  Disappointed.
You'll be sorry.
[music]
Sorry.   Say
sorry.  Say sorry.  Peace.
You just love me [music] and
we're happy.  Swy.
You won't be sorry.   I'm
sorry.   I'm
sorry.  I'm sorry.  Peace.
You only love me when we are happy.
You're angry and you apologize.   Say
sorry.  Say sorry.   Say
sorry.  Please.
Very angry.
You're going to apologize.   Say
sorry.  Say sorry.   Say
sorry.  Please.
You only love me when we are happy.
Very angry.  Do you only love me when
we are happy?
[cheers]
[applause]
Okay.  Let's see if Briana will win
this round.  And the
next obstacle is
strength.   Just
wait,
I brought a chair.  Can
I join the acting?
Mitch, the number you can't
choose is 1678 9 10.
Um, number four please.  Number four, Miles.
The only remaining numbers Miles has are 4
and nine.  Nine, please.  Number nine.  And you,
Justin?  Of course, I'm with the one
my love chose.  The number four
you chose, Mitch, is don't be a
victim.  You are not the victim.
You were just lied to.   It
suits you and for you, Miles,
you chose number nine.  How can you be
proud of something
you didn't work for?
And you, Justin, why is it so
hard for you to accept that
I'm right and you're wrong?
Mitch, you go first.  Ready?  It's ready
.  Okay.  Happy.  Don't be a victim.   I'm
not the victim.  You're
just lying.
Don't be a victim.  You are not the
victim.  You were just lied to.  Hey,
how can you be proud of
something you didn't work hard for?
But why is it so hard for you to accept it in
yourself?  I am right and you are wrong.  Where?
Don't be a victim.
I'm not the victim.  You're
just lying.
Don't be a victim.
You are not the victim.  You're
just lying.  You know how you can be
proud of something
you didn't work hard for?
Mitch,
why is it so hard for you to accept this
?  I was hit and miss.
[music]
Disappointed.
You know, Miles, don't be a victim.
You are the victim.  You're
just lying.
You know, Justine, don't be a victim.
the [music] is the victim.
You were just lied to.  How many miles is this?
How can you be proud of something
[music]
that you didn't work hard for?
Mitch, why is it so hard for you to accept
that I'm right and you're wrong?
Flirty.  [music]
You know, don't be a victim
because you're not the victim.
You're just lying.
You know, don't be a victim because
you're not the victim.  You're
just lying.  Mars
love, I just had to ask.  How can you be
proud of something
you didn't work hard for?
Justin
Mitch,
why is it so hard for you to accept
yourself?  [clears throat]
[music] I'm right and you're wrong.  angry
you know don't be a victim because
you're not the victim you're
just a liar really angry you know don't be a
victim because you're not
the victim you're just a liar really angry
you know don't be a victim because
you're not the victim
you're just a liar really
angry
you know don't be a victim because
I'm not the victim here.  You were just lied to
.
How can you be proud of something?
You worked hard.
Very angry.  Your skin is so thin, isn't it?
Your skin is so thin, isn't it?  How can you be proud
of something you didn't work for?
Angry Justin,
why is it so hard for you to accept
that I'm right and you're wrong?   Very
angry, what's wrong?
Why is it so hard for you to accept
that I'm right and you're wrong?  What?
Ouch!  I am hurt.
Sorry, sorry.  Stop it.
You're sick.  Oh, you're saying that's
too much.
Hey
[music]